ERIC JOSE JOY

Software Engineer

Contact

Address:

New Delhi, India, 110044

Phone:

+91-9970375650

Email:

ericjj94@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/eric-jose-319a91a2/

Skills

ReactJS: 4/5 Redux: 4/5

NodeJS: 4/5 HTML/CSS: 3/5

Javascript: 4/5 Jquery: 3.5/5

Enzyme: 4/5 Jest: 4/5

React Native: 2/5 Git: 4/5

Material UI: 4/5 Ant Design: 4/5

Projects

- 1. https://www.cofman.com Holiday home website in Europe that uses server side rendering in React
- https://www.heytravelista.com
 Hotel Booking Website in Hong Kong that uses
 Client side rendering with React
- 3. Admin Panel for Tekion Corp Client side rendered React Application
- 4. Mono Porto Parcel Delivery App React Native App for parcel delivery
- 5. PizzaMania

Pizza delivery website for users in Delhi/NCR

6. Abazeer

React Native app for organic food

Self-motivated Web Developer with 3.6 years of experience working on multiple projects. Passionate and hardworking with penchant for meeting deadlines. Interested in role with a company that promotes best practices and offers diverse customer projects.

Work History

Valuecoders LLP, April 2019- Present

Designation: Web Developer

- Worked as a ReactJS developer to develop Single page applications and write unit tests in enzyme,mocha and chai of the components created
- Worked on server side rendering with creating markup for SEO (both JSON-ld schema and microData).
- Projects URL: www.cofman.com, www.heytravelista.com

Greatwits Services Pvt Ltd, Feb 2018- March 2019

Designation: Software Developer

- Worked as a ReactJS developer to create single page applications with React and NodeJs as the backend.
- Project includes an admin panel created for Tekion Corp, USAthat allows the admin to make changes to the existing service menu admin of Tekion Corp.
- Developed a React Native app for a parcel delivery app(MonoPorto)

Greatwits Services Pvt Ltd, Sept 2017 - Jan 2018

Designation: Software Developer Trainee

• Worked as a trainee to learn the fundamentals of Web development that includes React and Redux as a single page application.

Artifici Labs Pvt Ltd, Jan 2017 - April 2017

Designation: Software Developer Intern

 Worked as an intern to learn the fundamentals of Web development that includes HTML/CSS and basics of Javascript and Jquery.

Education

July 2012- July Bachelors Of Engineering in Information Technology

Rashtrasant Tukadoji Maharaj Nagpur University, Maharashtra

Open source Contributions and Website Links

Portfolio: https://ejj-portfolio.herokuapp.com/

Github: https://github.com/ericjj94

Stackoverflow: https://stackoverflow.com/users/8917898/erick